{
  "quiz": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "title": "Matematika",
      "description": "Matematika",
      "question": "62825 Towne Lane",
      "active": true
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "title": "Fizika",
      "description": "Fizika",
      "question": "62825 Towne Lane",
      "active": false
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "title": "Kémia",
      "description": "Kémia",
      "question": "62825 Towne Lane",
      "active": false
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "title": "Biológia",
      "description": "Biológia",
      "question": "62825 Towne Lane",
      "active": false
    }
  ],
  "question": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "2+2?",
      "answers": ["4","5","6", "7"],
      "correct": "4",
      "points": 1,
      "active": true
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "5*8?",
      "answers": ["40","45","52", "85"],
      "correct": "40",
      "points": 1,
      "active": true
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Gravitáció?",
      "answers": ["F","G","g", "K"],
      "correct": "F",
      "points": 1,
      "active": true
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Energia?",
      "answers": ["E","N","R", "S"],
      "correct": "E",
      "points": 1,
      "active": false
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Natrium?",
      "answers": ["Na","Cu","Zn", "Fe"],
      "correct": "Na",
      "points": 1,
      "active": false
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Klór?",
      "answers": ["Cl","Br","Ca", "Fe"],
      "correct": "Cl",
      "points": 1,
      "active": false
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "DNS?",
      "answers": ["dezoxiribonukleinsav ","ribonukleinsav ","dezoxinukleinsav ", "dezoxiribosav "],
      "correct": "dezoxiribonukleinsav",
      "points": 1,
      "active": false
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "RNS?",
      "answers": ["ribonukleinsav ","nukleinsav ","ribosav ", "dezoxiribonukleinsav"],
      "correct": "ribonukleinsav",
      "points": 1,
      "active": false
    }
  ],
  "student": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "Enikő",
      "email": "eniko@gmail.com",
      "points": 0,
      "active": true
    } 
  ]
}